[
  {
    "title": "Hamas rejects Biden's optimism over ceasefire deal | World News | Sky News",
    "date": null,
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "Benjamin Netanyahu",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Joe Bidens",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Hamas",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Biden",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "World News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Lebanon",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "US",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "Benjamin Netanyahu",
      "Joe Bidens",
      "Hamas",
      "Biden",
      "World News",
      "Sky News",
      "Lebanon",
      "US"
    ],
    "snippet": "Hamas's spokesman in Lebanon tells Sky News the US president is just trying to \"keep everything sounding positive in the media\" and that Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu has made things \"more...",
    "source_file": "179b926ff00e34588d53fbcadeb42ee09c593219874ad22aef2cf69adaebc269/850e4065c41ec977e7a73ab3935c916a05b2daa0ff303f8d11c37f6161132e0b.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "Israel-Hamas war: Rishi Sunak fails to endorse calls for ceasefire | Politics News | Sky News",
    "date": null,
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "Rishi Sunak",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Stephen Flynn",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Politics News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "The Labour Party",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Hamas",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Israel",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Gaza",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "Rishi Sunak",
      "Stephen Flynn",
      "Politics News",
      "Sky News",
      "The Labour Party",
      "Hamas",
      "Israel",
      "Gaza"
    ],
    "snippet": "The Labour Party has also rejected calls for a ceasefire, arguing that Israel has the \"right to defend itself\" and to do what is needed to recover the 199 hostages held captive in Gaza. Political repo...",
    "source_file": "1f569eee2b31d86e556d2d9ee6ad2a4181535a0adb43afdb924bfce2189100f7/b835c8020cbd752e0fa75bc73f8e0b5bc162fd76cb5531d5be289fe8a450aadf.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "Kamala Harris tells Benjamin Netanyahu she will 'not be silent' over suffering in Gaza while stressing Israel's 'right to defend itself' | World News | Sky News",
    "date": null,
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "Kamala Harris",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Benjamin Netanyahu",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Joe Biden",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Claire Gilbody Dickerson",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "World News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Hamas",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Democratic Party",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "Kamala Harris",
      "Benjamin Netanyahu",
      "Joe Biden",
      "Claire Gilbody Dickerson",
      "World News",
      "Sky News",
      "Hamas",
      "Democratic Party"
    ],
    "snippet": "The likely Democratic presidential nominee appeared more strident than Joe Biden when it came to expressing her views on Israel's war on Hamas in Gaza. By Claire Gilbody Dickerson, news reporter Frida...",
    "source_file": "1e64a5f019427d3914eb74f395970a52b5953de876139c7081b9bfb35ca2c225/ca58af85d131042264a83e1449e65830ca2fa6eacb3498379ca480fd969e4611.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "Held in captivity: Faces of hostages taken on 7 October who still haven't returned home to Israel | World News | Sky News",
    "date": null,
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "Hamasfreed",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "World News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Hamas",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Israel",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "UK",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Gaza",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "politics",
        "type": "TOPIC",
        "source": "transformer",
        "score": 0.32
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "Hamasfreed",
      "World News",
      "Sky News",
      "Hamas",
      "Israel",
      "UK",
      "Gaza",
      "politics"
    ],
    "snippet": "With prisoner swaps underway between Hamas and Israel, the fates of almost 80 hostages taken by Hamas during the attack on 7 October 2023 are still unknown. Saturday 1 February 2025 07:23, UK With a r...",
    "source_file": "b3b4d7d94d55a4d353c018cc6991af4247fe2d61d5ecfbc6bf53990e43f93011/418cdd7db44b5118a310442c6d4a45cfb82287485be7284f75461c3809b81b3e.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "Trevor Phillips | Sky News",
    "date": null,
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "Trevor Phillips",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Trevor",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Webber Phillips",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sophy Ridges",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Royal Television Society",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Times",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "UK",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "Trevor Phillips",
      "Trevor",
      "Webber Phillips",
      "Sky News",
      "Sophy Ridges",
      "Royal Television Society",
      "Times",
      "UK"
    ],
    "snippet": "Trevor presents Sunday Morning from 8:30am each weekend. He previously presented Sky News’ Sunday politics show, covering for Sophy Ridge’s maternity leave in 2021, when he became the first black host...",
    "source_file": "eacb8a75aefdcd11dd40234822a0a1213dfdf17b46bed9e339c3387310edcf84/584b3ed169d931bb2877d80909dcbb082a11fe0f31e7e16eff22b46384356fd6.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "Pagers explode across Lebanon 'killing 9' and 'injuring thousands' - including Hezbollah members | World News | Sky News",
    "date": null,
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "Hassan Nasrallah",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Firas Abiad",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "World News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Hezbollah",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Hezbollahsaid",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Lebanon",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Israel",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "Hassan Nasrallah",
      "Firas Abiad",
      "World News",
      "Sky News",
      "Hezbollah",
      "Hezbollahsaid",
      "Lebanon",
      "Israel"
    ],
    "snippet": "Hezbollah leader Hassan Nasrallah previously warned the group's members not to carry mobile phones alleging Israel could use them to track their movements. Wednesday 18 September 2024 06:17, UK Please...",
    "source_file": "e9c5cbaae21f7993fc27afebed32c3b575b4c563267c78f22a9367b4a7dbe0df/4bef44dd0ef43a403030e2bb7a4291cb5a28521cdeb28708a7103375651f5c85.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "Arrest warrants issued for Israeli PM Netanyahu and former defence secretary Gallant and senior Hamas commander over alleged war crimes | World News | Sky News",
    "date": null,
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "Gallant",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Mohammed Deif",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Arrest",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Benjamin Netanyahu",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Yoav Gallant",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Hamas",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "World News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "Gallant",
      "Mohammed Deif",
      "Arrest",
      "Benjamin Netanyahu",
      "Yoav Gallant",
      "Hamas",
      "World News",
      "Sky News"
    ],
    "snippet": "An arrest warrant was also issued for Hamas leader Mohammed Deif, whom Israel claims to have killed earlier this year. Foreign news reporter@MikeRDrummond Friday 22 November 2024 07:12, UK Please use ...",
    "source_file": "43094bfaa736b670127571894d4e5d02a495ccae5527377ffec1d2970ce5e642/c9a7cdd57de4640e1f0d33367cb917008f3dc46d6bf31486c696def32d79744c.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "Israel-Hamas war: The truce has ended - why have negotiations stalled and what will Israel do now? | World News | Sky News",
    "date": null,
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "World News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Hamas",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "the Israel Defence Forces",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Israel",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "UK",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Gaza",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "business",
        "type": "TOPIC",
        "source": "transformer",
        "score": 0.25
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "World News",
      "Sky News",
      "Hamas",
      "the Israel Defence Forces",
      "Israel",
      "UK",
      "Gaza",
      "business"
    ],
    "snippet": "Israel has two stated goals: release all hostages and destroy Hamas. The truce proved an effective way of releasing hostages, but now that the war has resumed what will Israel's next step be? Military...",
    "source_file": "88045b3bf8f638dc6b8654dd18e85c310b23e5d741d765e89cb03a926b8f6e8c/0de0a8d5e7cbe0510959b5a999a83c6992875d8a33511bcb77bd315ce25a8410.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "Alix Culbertson | Sky News",
    "date": null,
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "Alix Culbertson",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Alix",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Westminster",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "politics",
        "type": "TOPIC",
        "source": "transformer",
        "score": 0.95
      },
      {
        "text": "entertainment",
        "type": "TOPIC",
        "source": "transformer",
        "score": 0.01
      },
      {
        "text": "technology",
        "type": "TOPIC",
        "source": "transformer",
        "score": 0.01
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "Alix Culbertson",
      "Sky News",
      "Alix",
      "Westminster",
      "politics",
      "entertainment",
      "technology"
    ],
    "snippet": "Alix is a political reporter, covering events in British politics from Westminster....",
    "source_file": "4f04e5962fa6eb1d3291d0249479845df2af56616e21e685bfffc84d8054e85b/b0304600267d3e996fa538a157ca4f6f6bf75782d59b830d83526f1bd0a8df29.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "Anger As Chilcot Delays Iraq Report Until 2016 | Politics News | Sky News",
    "date": null,
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "Chilcot",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "David Cameron",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "John Chilcot",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Politics News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "the Iraq Inquiry",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Iraq",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "UK",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "Chilcot",
      "David Cameron",
      "John Chilcot",
      "Politics News",
      "Sky News",
      "the Iraq Inquiry",
      "Iraq",
      "UK"
    ],
    "snippet": "David Cameron says he is \"disappointed\" Sir John Chilcot will not publish his long-awaited Iraq inquiry report until next year. Thursday 29 October 2015 10:19, UK Please use Chrome browser for a more ...",
    "source_file": "bacc90354d40e20d208297246076ba114c69cf218a142b32d90ed121b012c4ce/1e538a8ccca2a9cba309dea9d9172b2f0605b1f9d3b351475b592997340f045b.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "Funeral for five journalists killed in Israeli airstrike in Gaza | World News | Sky News",
    "date": null,
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "World News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Islamic Jihad",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Gaza",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Israel",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "UK",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "health",
        "type": "TOPIC",
        "source": "transformer",
        "score": 0.43
      },
      {
        "text": "entertainment",
        "type": "TOPIC",
        "source": "transformer",
        "score": 0.18
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "World News",
      "Sky News",
      "Islamic Jihad",
      "Gaza",
      "Israel",
      "UK",
      "health",
      "entertainment"
    ],
    "snippet": "Israel has claimed members of the Islamic Jihad militant group were inside the van, which was marked \"press\". Thursday 26 December 2024 14:47, UK Please use Chrome browser for a more accessible video ...",
    "source_file": "5d4b0401e8dbae0bbc3bc8b0f8c3313bd665efcf68a345778c685f36d7114ead/3c9ec2d745ef65831e4c4bb19d262b587fb09f048b42af5c533c5c6ec922fb11.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "Israel-Hamas war: A timeline of events since the 7 October attacks - and how Iran and Hezbollah became involved | World News | Sky News",
    "date": null,
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "Hezbollah",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "World News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Hamas",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Israel",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Iran",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Gaza",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "UK",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "Hezbollah",
      "World News",
      "Sky News",
      "Hamas",
      "Israel",
      "Iran",
      "Gaza",
      "UK"
    ],
    "snippet": "It has been more than a year since Hamas's 7 October attack on Israel, and the ensuing months have seen a war in Gaza that has killed tens of thousands and risked escalation elsewhere. In this story, ...",
    "source_file": "46785b53348eeb8e51b6c06953d9e49c63827ec1fcf280d550702e95f588781e/94575c05ac7968dbb6b998cd0a8524a42c057270ab301e62d6455a79114fd3c3.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "Israel-Hamas war: Three Britons killed in Gaza named, as IDF says 'misidentification' led to deadly airstrike | UK News | Sky News",
    "date": null,
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "John Chapman",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "James Kirby",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "James Henderson",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Three Britons",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "IDF",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "UK News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Israel",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "John Chapman",
      "James Kirby",
      "James Henderson",
      "Three Britons",
      "IDF",
      "UK News",
      "Sky News",
      "Israel"
    ],
    "snippet": "The three Britons are among seven aid workers who died after a convoy they were travelling in was hit as it was leaving a warehouse in Deir al Balah overnight. Wednesday 3 April 2024 10:35, UK Three B...",
    "source_file": "43ee70e878779b082590af39b9c3951fcc1479b1dee023997ca825731592574d/07a4a442d86299dd12b4ed12be45a868e6089f128fd28f0353db7c15dde4bda1.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "Benjamin Netanyahu says he and Donald Trump 'see eye to eye' on Iran | World News | Sky News",
    "date": null,
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "Benjamin Netanyahu",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Donald Trump",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "World News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Iran",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "US",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "America",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Israel",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "Benjamin Netanyahu",
      "Donald Trump",
      "World News",
      "Sky News",
      "Iran",
      "US",
      "America",
      "Israel"
    ],
    "snippet": "Foreign leaders are looking at the US to see how the upcoming change of administration will affect America's stance on Israel and Gaza. Sunday 10 November 2024 19:55, UK Benjamin Netanyahu says he and...",
    "source_file": "fb6fb2086cceaac65584761087d3ce23b66a6637a51b25af7690276cd02527e2/38072658312071148532913fe8b264a2dd8dec47ab85282639343e9b5b57b004.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "Israel-Hamas war: US vetoes UN resolution calling for ceasefire in Gaza - as UK explains why it abstained | World News | Sky News",
    "date": null,
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "UN",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "World News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "the United Nations Security Council",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Hamas",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "United Nations",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "the Security Council",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Israel",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "UN",
      "World News",
      "Sky News",
      "the United Nations Security Council",
      "Hamas",
      "United Nations",
      "the Security Council",
      "Israel"
    ],
    "snippet": "The US indicated it would veto the motion at the United Nations Security Council, arguing a ceasefire could leave Hamas in charge of the territory while still holding more than 100 hostages. Saturday ...",
    "source_file": "f0a7cdf961d269a7f65f053943f924f7db72eadd0d863bc4a1cb3b29b0c3fb66/24c2b07ddc8b41408d7c0949b16c7111d038030c29624f5250d98a19b4c6ac29.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "Furious row after Labour MPs denied entry to Israel - as Lammy criticises 'disgraceful' Badenoch response | Politics News | Sky News",
    "date": null,
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "Labour",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Yuan Yang",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Abtisam Mohamed",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Lammy",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Politics News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Israel",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Badenoch",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "Labour",
      "Yuan Yang",
      "Abtisam Mohamed",
      "Lammy",
      "Politics News",
      "Sky News",
      "Israel",
      "Badenoch"
    ],
    "snippet": "Yuan Yang and Abtisam Mohamed say they are \"astounded at the unprecedented step taken by the Israeli authorities\". Israel's UK embassy says they were denied entry because they had \"accused Israel of f...",
    "source_file": "397769131566300a5da97127cda515ce69e65174be4eacb409db0e720f8efadb/3a8809c106efc065b02484a06a837586f2233dca8162b3533050d566b2250a9e.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "Israel rescues four hostages from Gaza 'in good medical condition' | World News | Sky News",
    "date": null,
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "Noa Argamani",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "World News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Hamas",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Israel",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Gaza",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "UK",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "health",
        "type": "TOPIC",
        "source": "transformer",
        "score": 0.58
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "Noa Argamani",
      "World News",
      "Sky News",
      "Hamas",
      "Israel",
      "Gaza",
      "UK",
      "health"
    ],
    "snippet": "A video shows one of the hostages, Noa Argamani, being reunited with her father, smiling and hugging him and putting her head on his shoulder. The Hamas-run Gaza government media office says Israel ki...",
    "source_file": "d7bb3fc14b80eb7841e0dacc67b33238cdd284e7ac67740dcb9fa7dd5aefae7c/e85d515b99b3b9f1d37e0e10caf8b0c8f8b37a9ed65603661708a2e09809351a.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "UK will not oppose right of ICC to issue arrest warrant for Israeli PM Netanyahu, says No 10 | UK News | Sky News",
    "date": null,
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "Keir Starmers",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Benjamin Netanyahu",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Karim Khan KC",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "UK News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "the International Criminal Court",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Hamas",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "UK",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "Keir Starmers",
      "Benjamin Netanyahu",
      "Karim Khan KC",
      "UK News",
      "Sky News",
      "the International Criminal Court",
      "Hamas",
      "UK"
    ],
    "snippet": "A Downing Street spokesperson says the matter is solely one for the court and that it believes \"strongly in the rule of law and separation of powers\". Political reporter@alexrogerssky Friday 26 July 2...",
    "source_file": "1106c3ae50c623660a0d58c1267151110dc5559a2528b47367a1db3dc1984ea7/4c128d84d79a78ab4c47d52e7a5bfb40d385017a7f24c490e42f607770ffe499.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "Iran - The Latest News from the UK and Around the World | Sky News",
    "date": "2025-03-20 11:24:00",
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Iran",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "UK",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "entertainment",
        "type": "TOPIC",
        "source": "transformer",
        "score": 0.21
      },
      {
        "text": "economy",
        "type": "TOPIC",
        "source": "transformer",
        "score": 0.16
      },
      {
        "text": "business",
        "type": "TOPIC",
        "source": "transformer",
        "score": 0.12
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "Sky News",
      "Iran",
      "UK",
      "entertainment",
      "economy",
      "business"
    ],
    "snippet": "...",
    "source_file": "b417790061a36316c4c6cf6623643f33a218dfac65f7723ba032fed27c6a5318/f74fdf895f7527107f50c916f6a5f16fc0d6bc44c3cae85e01ed97254fda6d68.html"
  },
  {
    "title": " Keir Starmer has triggered a civil war with the left | Politics News | Sky News",
    "date": null,
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "Keir Starmer",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Politics News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Labour",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Deliveroo",
        "type": "PRODUCT",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "politics",
        "type": "TOPIC",
        "source": "transformer",
        "score": 0.89
      },
      {
        "text": "business",
        "type": "TOPIC",
        "source": "transformer",
        "score": 0.04
      },
      {
        "text": "health",
        "type": "TOPIC",
        "source": "transformer",
        "score": 0.02
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "Keir Starmer",
      "Politics News",
      "Sky News",
      "Labour",
      "Deliveroo",
      "politics",
      "business",
      "health"
    ],
    "snippet": "It is claimed the Labour leader had decided in advance on his course of action if his predecessor refused to apologise. Chief political correspondent@joncraig Friday 30 October 2020 16:11, UK Days aft...",
    "source_file": "7e3449334b37e4761114e5396f3302b22101ce356723922bf02cabdcf6c4a387/aec5402bd1b60bb0e4ef1dd5a9ef8f7e820d16ff80f04868f3273f0e6420b865.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "Sir Keir Starmer - The Latest News from the UK and Around the World | Sky News",
    "date": "2025-04-06 12:19:00",
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "Keir Starmer  The Latest News",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "UK",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "politics",
        "type": "TOPIC",
        "source": "transformer",
        "score": 0.27
      },
      {
        "text": "health",
        "type": "TOPIC",
        "source": "transformer",
        "score": 0.11
      },
      {
        "text": "business",
        "type": "TOPIC",
        "source": "transformer",
        "score": 0.1
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "Keir Starmer  The Latest News",
      "Sky News",
      "UK",
      "politics",
      "health",
      "business"
    ],
    "snippet": "...",
    "source_file": "1605cf88d90e4bedee6d5f118e36bf779fc2b2b760add9f07ae23f206bf12c38/684960085a52005371061a1c95c885e0602edfd50d4ae8e2c0b4a6cbea0654b9.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "Sunday Morning with Trevor Phillips",
    "date": "2025-03-31 07:49:00",
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "Trevor Phillips",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "entertainment",
        "type": "TOPIC",
        "source": "transformer",
        "score": 0.48
      },
      {
        "text": "business",
        "type": "TOPIC",
        "source": "transformer",
        "score": 0.09
      },
      {
        "text": "environment",
        "type": "TOPIC",
        "source": "transformer",
        "score": 0.08
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "Trevor Phillips",
      "entertainment",
      "business",
      "environment"
    ],
    "snippet": "...",
    "source_file": "e2d9540cdc95c04ff01c935fd4e3a91875c0966c7ec980a1f6fee2821cb79903/3eae7aca2368aa692f95c6398c5d26bc431a477f1b93786abf07487f18f7d22f.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "Sunday Morning with Trevor Phillips",
    "date": "2025-03-31 07:49:00",
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "Trevor Phillips",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "entertainment",
        "type": "TOPIC",
        "source": "transformer",
        "score": 0.48
      },
      {
        "text": "business",
        "type": "TOPIC",
        "source": "transformer",
        "score": 0.09
      },
      {
        "text": "environment",
        "type": "TOPIC",
        "source": "transformer",
        "score": 0.08
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "Trevor Phillips",
      "entertainment",
      "business",
      "environment"
    ],
    "snippet": "...",
    "source_file": "e2d9540cdc95c04ff01c935fd4e3a91875c0966c7ec980a1f6fee2821cb79903/93a2730039c432f129a62bc3743aa181370683e117d8885e466560fd2bfbcf68.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "Israeli military says it killed 'right-hand man to Hezbollah leader' in retaliatory strike on Beirut suburb | World News | Sky News",
    "date": null,
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "Fuad Shukr",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Hassan Nasrallah  in",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Haret Hreik",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Fuad Shukr",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "World News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "The Israel Defence Forces",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Hezbollah",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "Fuad Shukr",
      "Hassan Nasrallah  in",
      "Haret Hreik",
      "Fuad Shukr",
      "World News",
      "Sky News",
      "The Israel Defence Forces",
      "Hezbollah"
    ],
    "snippet": "The Israel Defence Forces (IDF) said it targeted Fuad Shukr - who served as the right-hand man to Hezbollah's secretary general Hassan Nasrallah - in the strike on Beirut's southern suburb of Haret Hr...",
    "source_file": "355cbe17674631446914868ef647b32fb56423e63fea62097c65e6ef34449fa9/5f19e76008de907cca098ddf94efcf7763cdc70e7c55db0de14597e2fffe1b9c.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "Qatar's PM says Israel-Hamas ceasefire deal is 'last chance for Gaza' | World News | Sky News",
    "date": null,
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "Yalda Hakim",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Mohammed bin Abdulrahman al Thani",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Donald Trump",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "World News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "withSky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Qatar",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "Yalda Hakim",
      "Mohammed bin Abdulrahman al Thani",
      "Donald Trump",
      "World News",
      "Sky News",
      "Sky News",
      "withSky News",
      "Qatar"
    ],
    "snippet": "Speaking exclusively to Sky News' Yalda Hakim, Sheikh Mohammed bin Abdulrahman al Thani spoke about peace in Gaza, Donald Trump and the need for a Palestinian state. Friday 17 January 2025 16:34, UK P...",
    "source_file": "0afcf24d97477ef67efd88d45f2f63fe47021daee96e70aaa56b6e1e14e6bfe7/5eb62351d0338eb211469c6e345755a2adc32d428c7c6643c78e2ebf9df92037.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "What happened to the Israel-Hamas ceasefire - and could there be another one? | World News | Sky News",
    "date": null,
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "World News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Hamas",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Israel",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Gaza",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "UK",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "politics",
        "type": "TOPIC",
        "source": "transformer",
        "score": 0.28
      },
      {
        "text": "business",
        "type": "TOPIC",
        "source": "transformer",
        "score": 0.18
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "World News",
      "Sky News",
      "Hamas",
      "Israel",
      "Gaza",
      "UK",
      "politics",
      "business"
    ],
    "snippet": "No major fighting had occurred in Gaza since the implementation of a three-stage ceasefire deal, until now. But what did the original ceasefire say - and what could a longer deal look like? Monday 24 ...",
    "source_file": "9ed0a57f70e00a0fce9b2b3eb92b0a831e1ac9210ebe2578900bbc34c08adb9d/f4cd508acbf6615688edc3372707d71653f853a07e09ea0a1fd747dc58b02238.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "Myanmar earthquake: Survivors' footage shows what it's like to be trapped in rubble | World News | Sky News",
    "date": null,
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "Dan Cairns",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "World News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Myanmar",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "UK",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "technology",
        "type": "TOPIC",
        "source": "transformer",
        "score": 0.26
      },
      {
        "text": "health",
        "type": "TOPIC",
        "source": "transformer",
        "score": 0.17
      },
      {
        "text": "economy",
        "type": "TOPIC",
        "source": "transformer",
        "score": 0.15
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "Dan Cairns",
      "World News",
      "Sky News",
      "Myanmar",
      "UK",
      "technology",
      "health",
      "economy"
    ],
    "snippet": "The three family members waited for hours to be rescued after their apartment block in Mandalay collapsed as they ran for the exit. By Dan Cairns, news reporter Monday 31 March 2025 13:21, UK Please u...",
    "source_file": "6ae096a736d752126c2fe812b720323cbd78cf0505bd9e8c52f10f85c1447746/bd604ed8d6e16ba439721bb2a3321fa30e576e1de917fe173ab3dedbd63d9f1a.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "Shiri Bibas 'mix-up' row: A fragile Gaza ceasefire stumbles from one hurdle more painful than the last | World News | Sky News",
    "date": null,
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "Shiri Bibas",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Diana Magnay",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "World News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Hamas",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Gaza",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "UK",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "Shiri Bibas",
      "Diana Magnay",
      "World News",
      "Sky News",
      "Hamas",
      "Sky News",
      "Gaza",
      "UK"
    ],
    "snippet": "The best possible outcome in a terrible situation is that Hamas finds the remains of Shiri Bibas and fast, writes Sky News' international correspondent Diana Magnay. International correspondent@DiMagn...",
    "source_file": "bdac27e51be992732447f50248c09a6d48a0c401094d66335e4657fa61a5f7a2/b42ad6869077cd40c1b86d164e7b88af474f3feb6574e83d6b65e8596ea9b31f.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "Israel says it's carried out 'pre-emptive' airstrikes in Lebanon - as Hezbollah fires back | World News | Sky News",
    "date": null,
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "Hezbollah",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "World News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Israel",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Lebanon",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "UK",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "politics",
        "type": "TOPIC",
        "source": "transformer",
        "score": 0.27
      },
      {
        "text": "technology",
        "type": "TOPIC",
        "source": "transformer",
        "score": 0.16
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "Hezbollah",
      "World News",
      "Sky News",
      "Israel",
      "Lebanon",
      "UK",
      "politics",
      "technology"
    ],
    "snippet": "Israel has carried out \"pre-emptive\" strikes against Hezbollah, while the militant group says it has completed the \"first phase\" of an attack on 11 Israeli military sites. Sunday 25 August 2024 14:00,...",
    "source_file": "0bd98d607eeef0cb7bbd48ca549d15373c0366a86d7d773ea12cfd03cee9a818/4f2593ca16b0c29bb088a12c622321056f93a8a53464221aabbbe5a127d996ec.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "What satellite images tell us about North Gaza as report accuses Israel of 'ethnic cleansing' | World News | Sky News",
    "date": null,
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "OSINT producerOliveLineham",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Joyce Msuya",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "World News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "UN",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Hamas",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "North Gaza",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Israel",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "OSINT producerOliveLineham",
      "Joyce Msuya",
      "World News",
      "Sky News",
      "UN",
      "Hamas",
      "North Gaza",
      "Israel"
    ],
    "snippet": "The Israeli military's latest offensive in northern Gaza began last month. While it's difficult to understand the full extent of the operation with independent media access into Gaza denied by Israel,...",
    "source_file": "bac3e5dcefe4c2c329fbd5fa60f0ea4123ca4b25243e8aa885fc013c9a2ba53d/6adfc7231074ecbb188475de7695a92e89431eeafd796d8459f29e390ab1b871.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "Hezbollah leader accuses Israel of targeting '5,000 people in two minutes' as he admits Lebanon blasts are 'unprecedented blow' | World News | Sky News",
    "date": null,
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "Hassan Nasrallah",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Hezbollahleader Hassan Nasrallah",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Hezbollah",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "World News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Israel",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Lebanon",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Beirut",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "Hassan Nasrallah",
      "Hezbollahleader Hassan Nasrallah",
      "Hezbollah",
      "World News",
      "Sky News",
      "Israel",
      "Lebanon",
      "Beirut"
    ],
    "snippet": "Sonic booms shook buildings over Beirut during the televised speech by Hezbollah leader Hassan Nasrallah as Israeli jets flew over the Lebanese capital. Friday 20 September 2024 00:07, UK Hezbollah's ...",
    "source_file": "da47257ccbb88ea3c653234984c2281ce6d679c94908867624e1674b76e7bbdf/c31c215c8face8f2e8ec23092d7ba0d475885d9b14ee80ce4726f1571d8e00de.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "Israel and Hamas agree to brief ceasefires in Gaza to distribute thousands of polio vaccines, WHO says | World News | Sky News",
    "date": null,
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "Hamas",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "WHO",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "World News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "The United Nations",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "the World Health Organisation WHO",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "coveri",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Israel",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "Hamas",
      "WHO",
      "World News",
      "Sky News",
      "The United Nations",
      "the World Health Organisation WHO",
      "coveri",
      "Israel"
    ],
    "snippet": "The United Nations is hoping to vaccinate an estimated 640,000 children in Gaza after traces of the polio virus were found in the sewage system earlier this year. Middle East correspondent@AliBunkallS...",
    "source_file": "6fec846a543ebafbff44526af2fe2139f158a35e15fd0de8e16a24f35210b7d9/c008ca74d79b57d0e065199760a076c3fa31603d9c936ad41f68791f62a17d4c.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "Why is Israel bombing Syrian airbases? | World News | Sky News",
    "date": null,
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "Bashar al Assads",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "World News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Israel",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Damascus",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "UK",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Syria",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "politics",
        "type": "TOPIC",
        "source": "transformer",
        "score": 0.29
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "Bashar al Assads",
      "World News",
      "Sky News",
      "Israel",
      "Damascus",
      "UK",
      "Syria",
      "politics"
    ],
    "snippet": "Israel has denied claims that its tanks have been advancing towards the Syrian capital, Damascus, but says it has been taking \"limited and temporary measures\" to protect its security. Foreign news rep...",
    "source_file": "94aa9aa6a1a082d3acbe00c3bd4936ac8c27467bdbea483463fae5e3dece7318/98a08e484d06d9fc44cbc021b54bd4bc85e2329d5fd9264de0b123e403837448.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "Downing Street indicates Netanyahu would be arrested in UK after ICC warrant | Politics News | Sky News",
    "date": null,
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "Netanyahu",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Benjamin Netanyahu",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Politics News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "The International Criminal Court",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "UK Downing Street",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "UK",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Gaza",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "Netanyahu",
      "Benjamin Netanyahu",
      "Politics News",
      "Sky News",
      "The International Criminal Court",
      "UK Downing Street",
      "UK",
      "Gaza"
    ],
    "snippet": "The International Criminal Court issued an arrest warrant for Benjamin Netanyahu on Thursday for alleged war crimes and crimes against humanity related to the war in Gaza. Political reporter@alixculbe...",
    "source_file": "202d683f25a08d05defc16a9e0758f495c585eb8ff68c81724d60734a2fc708f/f2b9f70fd95a5ba7086de366b026d2f7d6e1b8726123de2f660aaa7f256efdcc.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "Instagram apologises after inserting 'terrorist' into some Palestinian profiles | Science, Climate & Tech News | Sky News",
    "date": null,
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "emoji",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Science Climate  Tech News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Meta",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "UK Meta",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Instagram",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "technology",
        "type": "TOPIC",
        "source": "transformer",
        "score": 0.47
      },
      {
        "text": "science",
        "type": "TOPIC",
        "source": "transformer",
        "score": 0.31
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "emoji",
      "Science Climate  Tech News",
      "Sky News",
      "Meta",
      "UK Meta",
      "Instagram",
      "technology",
      "science"
    ],
    "snippet": "Meta said it had fixed a problem that \"briefly caused inappropriate Arabic translations\" after a user said his bio was auto-translated to: \"Praise be to God, Palestinian terrorists are fighting for th...",
    "source_file": "81641c9341e3f267e3feb4eeae06ee952b52f2a9944646e3c3b5e99c6717ed8b/da4b13e869476940ea8f100b6cc4f43d26269a47e2849c010ea56d029dca2c2f.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "Politics latest: Badenoch says she 'respects' Israel's decision to deny entry to Labour MPs | Politics News | Sky News",
    "date": null,
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "Trevor Phillips",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Map",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "MPs Yuan Yang",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Abtisam M",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Labour",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Politics News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky Newss",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "Trevor Phillips",
      "Map",
      "MPs Yuan Yang",
      "Abtisam M",
      "Labour",
      "Politics News",
      "Sky News",
      "Sky Newss"
    ],
    "snippet": "Speaking on Sky News's Sunday Morning With Trevor Phillips programme, the Conservative leader says: \"I think that every country should be able to control its borders, and that's what Israel is doing, ...",
    "source_file": "409a82ec660dab6c886f94ce35704103ff9ef602f22bcbe687c9a3ff03709aad/1b77f85f04dd677e59a093e5f736812bb7a25d8caa19e0648569636cf80558ae.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "Jeremy Corbyn accuses Labour of 'shameful attack' after he is blocked from standing for party | Politics News | Sky News",
    "date": null,
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "Jeremy Corbyn",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Labour",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Keir Starmer",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Politics News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "National Executive Committee",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "NEC",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "UK",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "Jeremy Corbyn",
      "Labour",
      "Keir Starmer",
      "Politics News",
      "Sky News",
      "National Executive Committee",
      "NEC",
      "UK"
    ],
    "snippet": "Labour's National Executive Committee (NEC) has backed a motion from leader Sir Keir Starmer saying it will not endorse his predecessor. Political reporter@fayebrownSky Wednesday 29 March 2023 07:07, ...",
    "source_file": "054a1fdd9ccb79506fe85a98df619a1cb57a6b4b9c992320d1f7a3602c6d6fdb/7fe000416d84d6fa9dd07ce9e766757610427939a41eb2a5fa85d4827930e6b2.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "The competing plans for rebuilding Gaza after the war | World News | Sky News",
    "date": null,
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "Donald Trump",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "World News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "theHamasattacks",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Gaza",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "US",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "UK",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Israel",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "Donald Trump",
      "World News",
      "Sky News",
      "theHamasattacks",
      "Gaza",
      "US",
      "UK",
      "Israel"
    ],
    "snippet": "Arab nations have agreed plans to rebuild Gaza after the war, including details on who would run the territory - but Donald Trump wants to build a \"Riviera\" under US control. Wednesday 5 March 2025 19...",
    "source_file": "c5db71644d77222d47b019e5c9fc2c50a22451d79f0599d1809c278e9c5a9fea/f77f91d0d226592ec8902e7dcd83c1fd7040f2cbfc636dd868d92439e91629b9.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "Israel stopping all goods and supplies into Gaza - hours after agreeing ceasefire extension plan | World News | Sky News",
    "date": null,
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "Benjamin Netanyahu",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Steve Witkoff",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "World News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Hamas",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Witkoff",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Israel",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Gaza",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "Benjamin Netanyahu",
      "Steve Witkoff",
      "World News",
      "Sky News",
      "Hamas",
      "Witkoff",
      "Israel",
      "Gaza"
    ],
    "snippet": "According to reports, there have been disagreements over whether to continue on to phase two of the ceasefire, during which a permanent peace will be negotiated, or extend phase one. Sunday 2 March 20...",
    "source_file": "cdbf8e938f826b006964b44bd052d3e0a682a9cb62bbd7ad80abd89e13581a86/ec8e17c6962a771f76286eb1cb540da72b5241ffd42a443fb38fa6c4d54ebe50.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu says airstrike on Rafah which killed dozens was 'tragic mistake'  | World News | Sky News",
    "date": null,
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "Benjamin Netanyahu",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Rafah",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "World News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Hamas",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Gaza",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "UK",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Gazan",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "Benjamin Netanyahu",
      "Rafah",
      "World News",
      "Sky News",
      "Hamas",
      "Gaza",
      "UK",
      "Gazan"
    ],
    "snippet": "Medics in the southern Gaza city say the strikes hit an area of tents being used by displaced people. The Israeli military said it struck a Hamas compound with \"precise ammunition and on the basis of ...",
    "source_file": "ab3bdd3fddad0bbdf422113efb44da848768cf5d7b9f068fc0cd6b176bdbd494/30b9201e19112cdd8759ceb255adbec0dbbb7486a46a15968fd7fd71101650ec.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "Ceasefire deal with Hezbollah agreed by Israeli security cabinet, Benjamin Netanyahu's office says | World News | Sky News",
    "date": null,
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "Benjamin Netanyahus",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Benjamin Netanyahu",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Hezbollah",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "World News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "UK",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "politics",
        "type": "TOPIC",
        "source": "transformer",
        "score": 0.3
      },
      {
        "text": "technology",
        "type": "TOPIC",
        "source": "transformer",
        "score": 0.15
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "Benjamin Netanyahus",
      "Benjamin Netanyahu",
      "Hezbollah",
      "World News",
      "Sky News",
      "UK",
      "politics",
      "technology"
    ],
    "snippet": "The agreement would bring about an end to fighting that has seen more than 3,500 Lebanese killed and more than 15,000 injured in over a year. News reporter@samuelosborne93 Wednesday 27 November 2024 0...",
    "source_file": "37e809c0c83065c6e1f05618dad2e15e9e971057898927a2a2a940ef05a6bf82/dd9d89979aa4dc1936b5f509545fae71ae53ffe965288be78ab5e870aa8cb5b8.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "Trump says US will take over Gaza and all Palestinians should relocate | World News | Sky News",
    "date": null,
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "Donald Trump",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Benjamin Netanyahu",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Andy Hayes",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Claire Gilbody Dickerson",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Trump",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "World News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "US",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "Donald Trump",
      "Benjamin Netanyahu",
      "Andy Hayes",
      "Claire Gilbody Dickerson",
      "Trump",
      "World News",
      "Sky News",
      "US"
    ],
    "snippet": "Donald Trump described Gaza as \"hell\" and \"one of the meanest, toughest places on earth\" as Benjamin Netanyahu visited him at the White House. By Andy Hayes and Claire Gilbody Dickerson, news reporter...",
    "source_file": "a24d279d1b20aeb966d4e4152c2c5b6abc61eac3692e710e7fe42baf3fda5f90/b8367e447af8bde45c2c860b10f80aaa7eb55c5274fe6d11dbdac1c6a50d10ff.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "Hamas 'approves list of 34 hostages to be returned' - but Israeli PM's office contests claim | World News | Sky News",
    "date": null,
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "MinisterBenjamin Netanyahuhas",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Hamas",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "World News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Israel",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "UK",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Gaza",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "politics",
        "type": "TOPIC",
        "source": "transformer",
        "score": 0.54
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "MinisterBenjamin Netanyahuhas",
      "Hamas",
      "World News",
      "Sky News",
      "Israel",
      "UK",
      "Gaza",
      "politics"
    ],
    "snippet": "Israel and Hamas argued on Sunday over the details of an agreement to halt fighting in the war-ravaged territory and bring captives home. Sunday 5 January 2025 23:42, UK Hamas has approved a list of 3...",
    "source_file": "03e9a6909194d538c5fdeca56a6f31d5cba6ee1af387c9423d34f5b6a345cd06/a442f7512642168d05636d15565ad76282de5ef96093e13c19243e772de54dbe.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "Starmer faces calls for UK's role in Gaza war to be scrutinised in Chilcot-style inquiry | Politics News | Sky News",
    "date": null,
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "Jeremy Corbyn",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Keir Starmer",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Politics News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Labour",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "UK",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Gaza",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Chilcot",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "Jeremy Corbyn",
      "Keir Starmer",
      "Politics News",
      "Sky News",
      "Labour",
      "UK",
      "Gaza",
      "Chilcot"
    ],
    "snippet": "In a letter to the prime minister seen by Sky News, former Labour leader Jeremy Corbyn says UK officials may have been implicated in \"the gravest breaches of international law\". Political reporter@ale...",
    "source_file": "ae5c005ff02121572c12c7a16576d7d98916db8b04225bf4ebc5eda0ab51660c/5ced630876386600d85358fff82337742bd5a9eff7d77403e4ca74be4ce72e50.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "Marine Le Pen latest: Far-right leader speaks for first time after being barred from French presidential election | World News | Sky News",
    "date": null,
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "Marine Le Pen",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "World News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "National Rally",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "UK",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "politics",
        "type": "TOPIC",
        "source": "transformer",
        "score": 0.66
      },
      {
        "text": "technology",
        "type": "TOPIC",
        "source": "transformer",
        "score": 0.09
      },
      {
        "text": "business",
        "type": "TOPIC",
        "source": "transformer",
        "score": 0.05
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "Marine Le Pen",
      "World News",
      "Sky News",
      "National Rally",
      "UK",
      "politics",
      "technology",
      "business"
    ],
    "snippet": "The National Rally leader says she is \"innocent\" after she is convicted of embezzlement and banned from running for public office for five years. She receives a four-year jail sentence, with two years...",
    "source_file": "c98a74bc9b369dabcd89f5568fbe67e24fd6fc9c100ad058562cdf2ee23a5c6c/5d366084668f8855345b851c82053d50720242b519a7c27d63ce0b8010ed3a89.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "Hamas names mastermind behind 7 October attack Yahya Sinwar as new leader | World News | Sky News",
    "date": null,
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "Ismail Haniyeh",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Hamas",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "World News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Tehran",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "UK",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Israel",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Yahya Sinwar",
        "type": "LOC",
        "source": "spacy"
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "Ismail Haniyeh",
      "Hamas",
      "World News",
      "Sky News",
      "Tehran",
      "UK",
      "Israel",
      "Yahya Sinwar"
    ],
    "snippet": "The last leader of the militant group, political chief Ismail Haniyeh, was assassinated in Tehran last month. He was the pragmatic face of Hamas and said to be less hardline or militaristic than his s...",
    "source_file": "c1d8f2815fa7ec4df29033dd2ea1a353fcb3ba80a36c0949c064c927e1500675/ef54ea5aee562133bf903d281555e27c9a7ce63ab65d0a720d56b27240f945e8.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "Middle East on a knife edge on eve of Gaza ceasefire talks | World News | Sky News",
    "date": null,
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "World News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Hezbollah",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Hamas",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Gaza",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "UK",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Iran",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Israel",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "World News",
      "Sky News",
      "Hezbollah",
      "Hamas",
      "Gaza",
      "UK",
      "Iran",
      "Israel"
    ],
    "snippet": "The region is suspended between a potential ceasefire and a massively escalating conflict. International affairs editor@DominicWaghorn Wednesday 14 August 2024 12:11, UK On the eve of crucial Gaza cea...",
    "source_file": "207a20e950ea655656199db1e67cee937565207482bbb73f8bbfb62d164c261f/f18d2ad6cec4f7c6477acff9e322565ea1fcf186fceebc24cdbcd2f8259493df.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "Who's in, who's out? The 'coalition of the willing' that could secure peace in Ukraine | World News | Sky News",
    "date": null,
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "World News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Ukraine",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "UK",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "France",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Germany",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Poland",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Italy",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "World News",
      "Sky News",
      "Ukraine",
      "UK",
      "France",
      "Germany",
      "Poland",
      "Italy"
    ],
    "snippet": "The idea is being led by the UK and France, two of the most powerful militaries in Europe, but questions remain over who else could be involved. What about Germany, Poland and Italy? Foreign news repo...",
    "source_file": "0c1a3b4465c0adc7786b1617be498f276b1b7431b35d0f5cfac141f651325eba/64c13fee07f265ec635a3dfc23227f45220d18f7fee9643aeb77aa812c495188.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "Israel targets 7 October mastermind in airstrike Gaza officials say killed at least 90 | World News | Sky News",
    "date": null,
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "Mohammed Deif",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "World News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Hamas",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Israel",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Gaza",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "UK",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "health",
        "type": "TOPIC",
        "source": "transformer",
        "score": 0.28
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "Mohammed Deif",
      "World News",
      "Sky News",
      "Hamas",
      "Israel",
      "Gaza",
      "UK",
      "health"
    ],
    "snippet": "Hamas's military chief Mohammed Deif, who developed the militant group's network of tunnels and its bomb-making expertise, has previously survived seven Israeli assassination attempts and topped its m...",
    "source_file": "3abe41aaa7b528de8a9d0e33709c112ced340129b66c2a84dfc1dd7e4fe5c8bc/fd49edfd6f7074bb2aa519b38cfca95719fbc9eb3e80d77ac596eb4d2a3df8a4.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "Fresh Gaza peace talks begin - with Iran saying they 'will only hold back if ceasefire agreed' | World News | Sky News",
    "date": null,
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "Ismail Haniyeh",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Claire Gilbody Dickerson",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "World News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Hamas",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Hezbollah",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Gaza",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Iran",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "Ismail Haniyeh",
      "Claire Gilbody Dickerson",
      "World News",
      "Sky News",
      "Hamas",
      "Hezbollah",
      "Gaza",
      "Iran"
    ],
    "snippet": "Reports suggest Iran will only hold back from retaliating against Israel following the killing of Hamas leader Ismail Haniyeh and a Hezbollah top military commander if parties can agree to a ceasefire...",
    "source_file": "696dc3b71bcbed0db2aae395c1858528afe9a159a96a6b8d2781223bb50e1dc5/3ea4143cc1a3ffb0195c1632ee638d06cb25c66157369ed2d4f1602e87fee763.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "Israel - The Latest News from the UK and Around the World | Sky News",
    "date": "2025-04-06 16:35:00",
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Israel",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "UK",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "entertainment",
        "type": "TOPIC",
        "source": "transformer",
        "score": 0.23
      },
      {
        "text": "technology",
        "type": "TOPIC",
        "source": "transformer",
        "score": 0.12
      },
      {
        "text": "business",
        "type": "TOPIC",
        "source": "transformer",
        "score": 0.12
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "Sky News",
      "Israel",
      "UK",
      "entertainment",
      "technology",
      "business"
    ],
    "snippet": "...",
    "source_file": "6e93cc0ce7e40a9190f1c8c018edf86bc0688ac6444101ea88b0134d8d5e9c67/0be4ba92d5cb7d009fc7af615d781df3e4db6947b77ab5829da0ca1c47d09c4c.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "Aid charity to resume operations in Gaza following killing of seven aid workers | World News | Sky News",
    "date": null,
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "World News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "WCK",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Gaza",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "UK",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "business",
        "type": "TOPIC",
        "source": "transformer",
        "score": 0.17
      },
      {
        "text": "entertainment",
        "type": "TOPIC",
        "source": "transformer",
        "score": 0.16
      },
      {
        "text": "technology",
        "type": "TOPIC",
        "source": "transformer",
        "score": 0.13
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "World News",
      "Sky News",
      "WCK",
      "Gaza",
      "UK",
      "business",
      "entertainment",
      "technology"
    ],
    "snippet": "World Central Kitchen (WCK) says it will resume operations in Gaza following the death of seven aid workers who were killed in an Israeli military strike on 1 April. News reporter@thejournojames Monda...",
    "source_file": "556cd293808b751f3a35e21502dc4b4c0d3b27352b268fee59bd94b872873a0e/afc49e7a80b4f886b2ab36af58155bee33fb045bb107c13e58de1af830580497.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "Tanks gather near Israeli-Lebanon border - as defence minister holds talks over 'expansion' of IDF activity  | World News | Sky News",
    "date": null,
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "Hassan Nasrallah",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Yoav Gallant",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Gallant",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "World News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Hezbollah",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Beirut",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "UK",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "Hassan Nasrallah",
      "Yoav Gallant",
      "Gallant",
      "World News",
      "Sky News",
      "Hezbollah",
      "Beirut",
      "UK"
    ],
    "snippet": "The deployment comes after Hezbollah confirmed that its leader of more than three decades Hassan Nasrallah was killed in an Israeli airstrike in Beirut on Friday. Sunday 29 September 2024 05:35, UK Pl...",
    "source_file": "c1e9192085cceefa3b687fb59949d889efa91057bcbc2b8fcc36ad24a9960f5d/0b92fd1da33162129cb0c899ef9ce79fd97b3b547436d5cff11189b43ab78e3d.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "Hamas leader Ismail Haniyeh killed in Iran, group says | World News | Sky News",
    "date": null,
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "Ismail Haniyeh",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Guards",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Haniyeh",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Hamas",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "World News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Revolutionary Guards",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Iran",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "Ismail Haniyeh",
      "Guards",
      "Haniyeh",
      "Hamas",
      "World News",
      "Sky News",
      "Revolutionary Guards",
      "Iran"
    ],
    "snippet": "Iran's Revolutionary Guards said Ismail Haniyeh and one of his bodyguards were \"assassinated\" in the capital Tehran, Iranian state media reported. News reporter@samuelosborne93 Wednesday 31 July 2024 ...",
    "source_file": "035f612ef680f69a06b17e42dc605f4819164cf9c91e86af2e10df2a3e1efe4d/8bad4feb5b49cb6319b405fd5b7d6f3dedcf90f29756b6e819b2186fc7ae28c6.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "Hamas accepts Gaza peace deal as Israeli official says agreement is close but 'not there yet' | US News | Sky News",
    "date": null,
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "Donald Trump",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Joe Biden",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Hamas",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "US News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Gaza",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Doha",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "UK",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "Donald Trump",
      "Joe Biden",
      "Hamas",
      "US News",
      "Sky News",
      "Gaza",
      "Doha",
      "UK"
    ],
    "snippet": "A new round of ceasefire talks was held in Doha on Tuesday to finalise the remaining details related to a possible ceasefire deal. Wednesday 15 January 2025 05:03, UK US president-elect Donald Trump h...",
    "source_file": "fe9f9442e35b7dffda59fbdebcfd0d82125a244f3668407610d1bf7da1287679/2e567ab3c9c28d0d2c59dc4ad0c0ec8cddb3c442c086bed8791ccece98e27c76.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "Jeremy Corbyn - The Latest News from the UK and Around the World | Sky News",
    "date": "2025-03-26 17:03:00",
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "Jeremy Corbyn  The Latest News",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "UK",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "politics",
        "type": "TOPIC",
        "source": "transformer",
        "score": 0.7
      },
      {
        "text": "entertainment",
        "type": "TOPIC",
        "source": "transformer",
        "score": 0.07
      },
      {
        "text": "economy",
        "type": "TOPIC",
        "source": "transformer",
        "score": 0.05
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "Jeremy Corbyn  The Latest News",
      "Sky News",
      "UK",
      "politics",
      "entertainment",
      "economy"
    ],
    "snippet": "...",
    "source_file": "0682fe1d3e957942cececf62bbc4f890d31081d5c38a3eea151d54da07acdd41/0b787e8fb637b6071b0d9976ae9094bb76621fc56b003b5963684ae86db81505.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "Aerial footage shows moment British jets strike Houthi military targets in Yemen | World News | Sky News",
    "date": null,
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "Houthi",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "World News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Yemen",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "UK",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "US",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Iran",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "theIran",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "Houthi",
      "World News",
      "Sky News",
      "Yemen",
      "UK",
      "US",
      "Iran",
      "theIran"
    ],
    "snippet": "UK and US forces bombed more than a dozen sites used by the Iran-backed militia in a massive retaliatory strike for attacks on international shipping in the Red Sea. Friday 12 January 2024 10:58, UK P...",
    "source_file": "456901172376e583c284ddadf6d23cc7728a034cd1c4dba538a27065f7b856b5/3432afcdfa48607f55f3b4196c5003c75d9bbbb62cd7b666f8980e22727419b8.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "Conflicting claims about Gaza hospital blast. So who's said what? | World News | Sky News",
    "date": null,
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "al Ahli al Arabi",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "World News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "al Ahli hospital",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Hamas",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "the Palestinian Islamic Jihad",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Gaza",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Israel",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "al Ahli al Arabi",
      "World News",
      "Sky News",
      "al Ahli hospital",
      "Hamas",
      "the Palestinian Islamic Jihad",
      "Gaza",
      "Israel"
    ],
    "snippet": "Israel has said a misfired rocket from Gaza caused the explosion at al Ahli hospital, while Hamas and the Palestinian Islamic Jihad say Israel is to blame. Here is what we know so far about what happe...",
    "source_file": "bcf7a9954a5d65465ab92c9264e5f9f5e93682536f2679faec7637acd10670b4/cc94b5d101efef9d66a4291640d4e6cc78fb4779cb308fab709533ad8129529e.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "Gaza: 'Horror movie' scenes as Hamas says 210 Palestinians killed in area of Israeli hostage rescue mission | World News | Sky News",
    "date": null,
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "Horror",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Hamas",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "World News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Gaza",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "UK",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Israel",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "health",
        "type": "TOPIC",
        "source": "transformer",
        "score": 0.2
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "Horror",
      "Hamas",
      "World News",
      "Sky News",
      "Gaza",
      "UK",
      "Israel",
      "health"
    ],
    "snippet": "Israeli forces rescued four hostages held by Hamas since October in a raid Palestinian officials said killed more than 200 people. The scenes were likened to a \"horror movie\" by one paramedic. Sunday ...",
    "source_file": "3e112281824f13d35cdca44c58b18f46cb4f8975e6711156d7defc860a0aa6c9/6e41b6acbc7ed2b14de8ac000e6c17bfd33b9a950256452a9740193e97da6e58.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "Hamas confirms death of leader Yahya Sinwar – as it vows not to return hostages until Israeli troops leave Gaza | World News | Sky News",
    "date": null,
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "Yahya Sinwar",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Daniel Binns",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Hamas",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "World News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sinwar",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Gaza",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "UK",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "Yahya Sinwar",
      "Daniel Binns",
      "Hamas",
      "World News",
      "Sky News",
      "Sinwar",
      "Gaza",
      "UK"
    ],
    "snippet": "Hamas says Sinwar's death would \"only increase the strength and resolve\" of its \"resistance\". By Daniel Binns, news reporter Friday 18 October 2024 17:14, UK Please use Chrome browser for a more acces...",
    "source_file": "134f9c5a121ab1f7488e58ca79577e453ecdad6feb2ab4cc0dc1a30de581c7de/09662fdc67a65fa8b7f1ea7dfc65400aeaa3b8df8110be68cdc6facda4adb419.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "Israel says Hamas decision to accept ceasefire deal is a 'ruse' | World News | Sky News",
    "date": null,
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "Hamas",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "World News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Israel",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Gaza",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "UK",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Egypt",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Qatar",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "Hamas",
      "World News",
      "Sky News",
      "Israel",
      "Gaza",
      "UK",
      "Egypt",
      "Qatar"
    ],
    "snippet": "Hamas has called on Israel to \"seize the moment\" after agreeing to a ceasefire deal that would pause the fighting in Gaza - but an Israeli official has said the \"softened\" proposal is \"not acceptable\"...",
    "source_file": "444ba3e388505739b7d3a615934daff8961eac16b56bb043dcaf54918fbab0aa/c04ddd2ac5e064fac03527207b0667f118bbffe9c13cd4917604de6d4d4f0313.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "Israel cuts power to Gaza after Hamas refuses to extend first phase of ceasefire deal | World News | Sky News",
    "date": null,
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "Hamas",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "World News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Israel",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Gaza",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "UK",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "politics",
        "type": "TOPIC",
        "source": "transformer",
        "score": 0.37
      },
      {
        "text": "business",
        "type": "TOPIC",
        "source": "transformer",
        "score": 0.18
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "Hamas",
      "World News",
      "Sky News",
      "Israel",
      "Gaza",
      "UK",
      "politics",
      "business"
    ],
    "snippet": "Following last week's decision to strip Gaza of all supplies of goods, Israel says it is now cutting off electricity to the besieged strip. It comes as Hamas wants to move on to the second phase of a ...",
    "source_file": "d02b250c05e8a5dedcb46e3112692b876b2b990187e143024bbae2e87fc6018a/559b807015ba09046bc38c6b845a6cbe3c6130e5ed2fb291e14772bf8f5d8a37.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "'They are a target in his eyes': IDF releases findings of what went wrong in strike that killed aid workers | World News | Sky News",
    "date": null,
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "Alistair Bunkall",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Katy Scholes",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "World News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "IDF",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "UK",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Middle East",
        "type": "LOC",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "business",
        "type": "TOPIC",
        "source": "transformer",
        "score": 0.14
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "Alistair Bunkall",
      "Katy Scholes",
      "World News",
      "Sky News",
      "IDF",
      "UK",
      "Middle East",
      "business"
    ],
    "snippet": "The IDF has released findings of a strike that killed seven aid workers - identifying that a series of mistakes and incorrect assumptions resulted in their deaths. By Alistair Bunkall, Middle East cor...",
    "source_file": "1f23fb03101f29fb916e8ebc312fa07e4587bb571e86388581e31e701edaf906/2334ae2d640769914400dc387d3c23617244ad83def11f9e55cffcbe5ec8ed4c.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "Politics latest: Badenoch says she 'respects' Israel's decision to deny entry to Labour MPs | Politics News | Sky News",
    "date": null,
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "Trevor Phillips",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Map",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "MPs Yuan Yang",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Abtisam M",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Labour",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Politics News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky Newss",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "Trevor Phillips",
      "Map",
      "MPs Yuan Yang",
      "Abtisam M",
      "Labour",
      "Politics News",
      "Sky News",
      "Sky Newss"
    ],
    "snippet": "Speaking on Sky News's Sunday Morning With Trevor Phillips programme, the Conservative leader says: \"I think that every country should be able to control its borders, and that's what Israel is doing, ...",
    "source_file": "32b7111bbe3022ea50aa27c5c22f410b23d671ff7459f96869528a37e5d1a2eb/1b77f85f04dd677e59a093e5f736812bb7a25d8caa19e0648569636cf80558ae.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "Benjamin Netanyahu - The Latest News from the UK and Around the World | Sky News",
    "date": "2025-04-02 06:25:00",
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "Benjamin Netanyahu",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "UK",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "politics",
        "type": "TOPIC",
        "source": "transformer",
        "score": 0.37
      },
      {
        "text": "entertainment",
        "type": "TOPIC",
        "source": "transformer",
        "score": 0.14
      },
      {
        "text": "business",
        "type": "TOPIC",
        "source": "transformer",
        "score": 0.09
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "Benjamin Netanyahu",
      "Sky News",
      "UK",
      "politics",
      "entertainment",
      "business"
    ],
    "snippet": "...",
    "source_file": "e3832a5db993f572bd574b04082d60ff5bffa39f776774a7f066dccac5fbe717/74f83ef38a559e89f6a049304a53be0ef82e5269181b57d59144014257365ec9.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "Virginia Giuffre, who accused Prince Andrew of sexual assault, says she has days to live after car crash | US News | Sky News",
    "date": null,
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "Virginia Giuffre",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Prince Andrew",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Andrew",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Virginia Guiffre",
        "type": "PERSON",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "US News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "the Duke of York",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "UK",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "Virginia Giuffre",
      "Prince Andrew",
      "Andrew",
      "Virginia Guiffre",
      "US News",
      "Sky News",
      "the Duke of York",
      "UK"
    ],
    "snippet": "Virginia Giuffre sued the Duke of York for sexual abuse in August 2021, saying Andrew had sex with her when she was 17. The duke has repeatedly denied the claims, and he has not been charged with any ...",
    "source_file": "7b21306640fece7d394a3ebb7ee4b365c019457dfc044fb11b6da2ae77594598/38f1fcad63e466a3368389a4c2c4a12b2b0b173769dd033195de59851799c19b.html"
  },
  {
    "title": "Israel-Hamas war: Israeli tanks spotted in centre of Rafah for first time after UN chief's 'hell on earth' comments | World News | Sky News",
    "date": null,
    "website": "Sky News",
    "keywords_data": [
      {
        "text": "UN",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "World News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Sky News",
        "type": "ORG",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Israel",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Rafah",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "Gaza",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "UK",
        "type": "GPE",
        "source": "spacy"
      },
      {
        "text": "politics",
        "type": "TOPIC",
        "source": "transformer",
        "score": 0.25
      }
    ],
    "keywords": [
      "UN",
      "World News",
      "Sky News",
      "Israel",
      "Rafah",
      "Gaza",
      "UK",
      "politics"
    ],
